[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Disclaimer: This series is created solely for entertainment purposes.
All individuals, behaviors, places, and events depicted are entirely fictional,
with no intention to represent or reference any organizations, departments, occupations, or individuals]
I don't want you to be in this terrible relationship.
You make the person you're with feel seen
and acknowledged.
That's the reason
I want to be your friend.
If you still hold each other back,
no one is going to be happy.
We were never friends, Chris...
What's most important about food is taste.
But taste is made up of texture,
smell,
experience,
and memory.
♫The rain keeps splashing beneath our cover,♫
♫Once it was a special place for two lovers♫
♫There was never enough room for the third♫
♫Now, the rain soaks our hearts together♫
♫The question that's trapped in my heart♫
♫Maybe it's time for you to do your part♫
♫Choose the one your heart truly desires♫
♫Before the last raindrop falls, don't make me shed another tear♫
Chris,
cooking with flowers
isn't easy.
That means it's possible?
Doing something and being good at it are two different things.
But I think
this is good.
I'm buying it,
both you...
and your food.
It's so good.
Really?
Well done.
You got it on your face.
Let's give it a try.
The terms remain the same.
You'll work behind the scenes,
and you can start the PR plan right away.
Mm.
Since she's already done this much...
Why not at least let her train the chefs?
As for the restaurant,
I'll take care of Chris.
If customers have questions,
she can answer them about her inspiration.
I'll take care of her.
Chris has to work mostly behind the scenes anyway.
Are you that happy?
Mm.
It feels like my abilities are being acknowledged for the first time.
Then, I'll come up with more dishes.
There should be a lot of dishes when you're promoting something new,
right?
I'll be back.
Did she really have to rush to come up with new dishes?
[COME AGAIN, WE'RE CLOSED]
[Calling]
Who are you calling?
A friend...
Your friend who helped you come up with the flower dishes?
Mm... yes.
That's nice.
I want to thank them as well
for making you want to help me with my work.
And for making us...
closer...
Don't do this, Nadear.
That's right.
When we dated,
you wouldn't even let me kiss you.
Why would I expect anything now?
What are you expecting?
Change, perhaps?
I was willing to accept your flower dishes
in hopes that
you'd let me...
back into our relationship.
Back, you say?
I used to be in here, didn't I?
If my brain has an issue,
would my feelings change too, Doctor?
The brain...
controls your emotions, Chris.
My brain tells me I love Nadear,
but my feelings say otherwise.
Who is right for you then?
Can I tell you that?
It's a matter of medical ethics.
A patient's information is confidential.
But you don't seem like that good of a person?
That's true,
but I'm a good friend.
A friend's code.
I'll keep my friend's secret to myself.
I loved Nadear in the past.
That means now...
If my memories returned,
would the Nadear I knew then
be the same person she is now?
Speaking as a doctor,
I'd say...
Our brains are complex.
And what if you answer as a friend?
Our hearts aren't as complex.
Chris is in love with someone else, isn't she?
I don't think so.
You're lying.
It might be that friend.
The one who taught her to make those flower dishes.
And if it's true...
what will you do?
I should be asking you that.
What should I do?
You have to let her go.
You know I can't do that.
What I mean is...
you need to give Chris more freedom.
Chris needs to be free
before she can choose who to love.
And what if she doesn't choose me?
Well, you have me.
Alright...
I'll give it a try.
You won't let Chris leave me, right?
This plant is hardy.
It's easy to take care of
and can purify the air as well.
Alright,
I'll help you out.
Oh, Chris?
Sun.
Is everything alright?
Why are you here?
I couldn't contact you.
Are you alright?
I'm alright.
What about you?
You're not okay, are you?
I did it.
I told you you got this.
It's all thanks to you.
Does coming here have something to do with me too?
I've always thought about you
ever since I made those dishes for the customers.
What were you thinking of me?
I think it's your compliments?
You always know what to say to cheer me up.
I kissed you,
because I don't want to be just friends.
What about you?
I don't love Nadear when I'm awake.
But every time I dream,
it's always about her.
The affection still lingers.
Your heart
might be more complex than your brain.
But be careful.
This won't only hurt you.
It'll hurt the others too.
So,
are we just friends?
Sun, you're a friend I never want to hurt.
Not even a little bit.
Doctor Prung,
you came in without saying anything.
Well, when my sister does something,
she doesn't seem to tell me either.
I didn't tell you,
but you knew anyway.
This is even worse, Jeen.
It's not.
We still have hope.
What hope?
Chris...
will never love Nadear.
Never.
That means...
Nadear
will love you.
Do you really think that?
It means...
this is the first time
I'll do the right thing.
Aw...
That's good.
[Third Person Bar - Bistro]
It seems like Chris
really enjoys working here.
Aren't you worried about her being stressed anymore?
I'm going to a flower farm. I'll be back in the evening.
With who?
A friend.
Her working here isn't as worrying as
going to the flower farm with her friend again.
Wow.
It seems like Chris
has friends other than you.
Yes.
It's a good thing
I have you, Nan.
You'll be by my side, right?
I have been with you all this time.
[Parking spot]
Is that your girlfriend?
Why don't you answer it?
[Nadear]
I'll go back soon.
I'll see you this evening.
You spoke so politely.
Not only is your girlfriend lucky,
but you're lucky to have her too, huh?
I wanted it to be that way too.
What is your girlfriend like?
Well...
She's a woman with long black hair,
and she smiles...
so much that I call her "Smiley."
Smiley...?
Smiley.
[Third Person]
The hotel
picked up the edible flowers a couple of hours ago.
It was an urgent order.
We truly apologize,
but we do have other products you can take a look at.
It's alright.
We came without an appointment.
Not even a little bit left...?
You have tulips here?
Yes.
Would you like to see them? I'll tell the employees to guide you there.
Yes, please.
Thank you.
Why are you smiling?
Let's take some photos together.
Let's go!
Let's take a picture.
Come on.
Here.
Chris, why are you looking at me like that?
I'm just a bit surprised.
I thought you only liked roses.
If someone changes what they like,
will their feelings stay the same?
If I like tulips,
not roses,
will you still want to be friends with me?
I like roses
because I like you.
But if you choose to like tulips,
I'll like them too.
Thank you.
Keep your promise, alright?
This feels familiar, huh?
But today isn't the same.
Why?
Because we're just friends.
Mm.
Can you tell me why?
The reason is...
Don't be a bad person because of me, Sun.
Do you have someone else?
Why do you ask me that?
Why aren't you denying it?
You do know
what our relationship is, don't you?
But we're still dating.
I won't let anyone come between us.
If I do, I'll tell you.
If you didn't,
then why did you change?
I can't even remember
who I used to be,
so how could I change?
But I do...
You used to care more about me.
You heard me out.
You listened to me.
You trusted me.
You never asked to break up with me.
You used to make me smile.
I want you to remember.
Chris!
Chris...
I've always looked at you...
I could feel your eyes
always watching me.
Is someone looking at me?
Yeah.
She didn't even look away.
Ugh, what the heck is wrong with her?
She's the new kid
we asked to join our group yesterday.
Huh?
Mm.
After talking to her...
she seems pretty nice.
She started school a month after us because...
she moved with her dad after he changed jobs.
Ow.
Chris!
You!
Run three laps around the field!
Hey! Be more careful.
Do you want to get caught buying stuff from outside the school?
Hey, you two!
What are you doing?!
Run!
Get up there!
Go!
Get down, get down.
Why did we have to run this far?
Well, I was scared.
Do you think...
he'll find us here?
Maybe he will
if you keep letting the smell of meatballs waft around like this.
Did you know?
This is my first time skipping class.
If you weren't waiting for your food out in the open like that,
you wouldn't have had your first time like this.
We had to run for our lives, you see?
It was fun, though.
Huh?
I said,
skipping class with you today was fun.
Want some?
Smiley...
It's me...
Please be alright...
You love the Nadear in your memories,
but you want to break up with this Nadear?
Why?
Nadear used to smile a lot,
until she loved me.
That's a classic reason
for breaking up.
Is it really for her?
Are you a psychiatrist or an expert at hitting a sore spot?
I told you, I'm your friend.
I even meet you outside.
If I could fall in love with Nadear from the past,
but not with
the Nadear I know now,
shouldn't that mean I should break up with her?
Does this have anything to do with the new friend you just met?
I never wanted to be just friends with her.
[Third Person]
You again?
Shouldn't I be asking you that?
You know full well the reason
people come here.
I can't contact Sun.
I know what Sun thinks of you,
but she can't move on from you because you act like this.
She already has a lot of problems in her life.
Can't you keep your distance from her?
Is there something going on?
Hello, Sun,
where are you?
Can we meet?
I want to talk about something.
Huh?
Then can I go with you?
Excuse me, I'd like to change my destination.
Okay.
[VERITY SKIN CLINIC]
How are you doing?
Is this cocoa?
I feel better now.
You're so stressed, aren't you?
Mm...
Looking at the expenses...
it's quite troubling to me.
I was in an accident,
so my father sent me abroad for treatment.
Now that I've recovered,
I want to repay my debts to my father.
But look at this...
An accident?
When did it happen?
Four years ago...
That was around the same time as mine.
Yeah.
There is so much to think about,
so everything seems necessary.
Actually, I have some savings...
Don't, Chris.
You've just said that we should be friends.
We've just known each other.
Don't do this...
How about this?
Let's do what you've told me before.
Choose what fits you perfectly
so you feel at ease
and not uncomfortable.
Then...
Can you stay here with me?
When I'm with you...
I feel exactly like that.
[VERITY SKIN CLINIC] ["Reveal The True You"]
Is there anything else you'd like to put in this room?
I think so.
Let me think about it.
Don't go over budget, okay?
I think this equipment can only be placed here.
But we already went way over budget.
If we buy this equipment,
we won't have enough money for the more important one.
If we put both pieces of equipment there,
it...it really won't work out.
Is there anywhere else we can cut back?
I agree with you, Doctor Sun.
This is perfect.
It's not very risky either.
I didn't come up with it.
Chris helped me.
Wow...
Iced lemon tea can help in hot weather like this.
- This is yours, Doctor. - Thank you.
Thank you.
Here.
This is yours.
Thanks.
Are you tired?
A little bit.
I'm impressed.
Ms. Chris, you're quite talented.
She's very detail-oriented
and caring.
That's nice.
Then...can we ask you to be our consultant?
Of course.
Thank you so much.
Here, I'll hold it for you.
Overall, this looks okay now.
I like being useful.
But right now...
I'm more curious about
how Sun acts like she knows me well.
Are you thanking me by buying me something you like to eat?
Give it a taste.
You might like it, Chris.
Yes,
I do like it...
How did she know that?
Your face is very telling.
You finally smiled.
Hm?
Well, you hardly smiled today.
My life isn't exactly full of things to smile about.
So...
You came to see me. Is something going on?
I came to see your smile.
Hm?
So...
Seen enough?
Didn't you say that Chris remembered dating me in high school?
Hello, Prung.
I'm sorry, I didn't see you there.
It's okay, Dear.
Prung...already knew everything.
Chris remembers that.
I already talked to her.
Then why isn't she falling for me yet?
She's a doctor,
not a shaman.
She can't make love potions.
Prung.
It's because you only focus on the past.
The "past" that can't be changed,
instead of the present.
It's not just about her amnesia,
but also about a relationship between lovers.
A relationship should be about the present.
You wouldn't understand
how important the "past"
is to me.
Are you sure you don't want me to drive you home?
You already have a lot to think about. Rest up.
Thanks.
Sun,
something sweet to help relieve stress.
I'll go now.
Mm.
♫Your smile is always so bright♫
♫The smile imprinted in my heart♫
♫Shining like the Sun♫
♫Providing warm embrace,♫
♫Always being near, hugging you tight,♫
♫So you don't shed a tear♫
♫If you had to face the storm,♫
Thank you...
♫The Sun will be there, shining in the sky♫
Thank you for not making me regret coming back here.
[Third Person]
[Happy Anniversary]
The accident that happened four years ago
almost took you away from me.
I called your name every day
until you regained consciousness.
But you kept staring out the window with tears in your eyes,
and refused to talk for five months.
You had severe depression.
Your body was wounded.
You were traumatized.
Your brain shut out the pain,
blocking out everything else.
Jeen.
Then you started to remember.
Here.
Did you buy these to give to people?
No,
they're offerings for Buddha.
Then no thanks. I don't want to take one meant for Buddha.
This one isn't an offering.
I want to give it to you.
You lost your parents in that accident,
while I...
I lost you.
I only thought
I wanted you to remember how we used to love each other.
I wanted our relationship to go back to how it used to be,
and that made me completely ignore what we have now.
I'm sorry.
Nadear...
Chris...
I asked you not to break up with me,
not because of my parents,
but because I love you.
Can you give me another chance?
I can't, Nadear.
I can't love you.
Chris, why?
You only have me.
The one who laughs while looking at you.
The one who skipped class with you.
The one who bought you roses.
It's all me, Chris.
That's not it.
That's not it, Nadear.
Chris...
I can't, I can't, I can't...
Nadear, this isn't right. I can't, it's...
Chris!
I don't know why I'm like this.
I don't want to keep living like this anymore, Nadear.
Chris...
Alright,
I give up.
Can you give me three months?
Three months to go back to how it used to be.
Then I won't ask anything from you again.
Chris, please?
[Happy Anniversary]
What do you mean, "three months"?
You broke up a long time ago,
but you plan to date her again for three months?
It's my final gambit.
What are you going to do?
I'll make Chris
mine...
by any means necessary.
So you acted weird
because you want to be friends with me
so that you can cut ties with your ex.
Mm...
But I couldn't do it.
And I even gave her three months.
You gave in because
you still love her, don't you?
She used to be someone important to me.
This sounds like we're having an affair.
I really don't want you to be a bad person because of me.
We were wrong from that very first kiss, Chris.
Will God punish us?
This pain
is God's punishment.
Can I still make things right?
Mm.
I'll wait.
Wait for what?
Three months might be long enough for you to love someone else.
Or it might be long enough for you to decide we should be just friends.
But three months
is long enough for you
to tell love from indebtedness.
I know what love is
ever since I first met you.
♫The rain keeps splashing beneath our cover,♫
♫Once it was a special place for two lovers♫
♫There was never enough room for the third♫
♫Now, the rain soaks our hearts together♫
♫The storm grows heavier, demanding an answer♫
I'll make things right
after three months.
Don't you think
she can keep asking for more time?
But it's important to me too.
It's really you, huh?
How was she doing
after that accident four years ago?
Sun lost her memories back then.
I think Sun got her memories back.
Sun...
is my friend...?
♫The rain keeps splashing beneath our cover,♫
♫Once it was a special place for two lovers♫
♫There was never enough room for the third♫
♫Now, the rain soaks our hearts together♫
♫The question that's trapped in my heart♫
♫Maybe it's time for you to do your part♫
♫Choose the one your heart truly desires♫
♫Before the last raindrop falls, don't make me shed another tear♫